[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Did you say \"Barbara\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "I said Barbra.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "How did you even know to buy a sports jacket?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I took a class in it, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "You also had a ball doing it, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Oh, if you like -- yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Do you hate all work, basically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "What do you like doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "I love -- I love making movies and I love recording.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "You consider yourself to be primarily an actress who sings, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Uh-huh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "The dream was always to be an actress, to be a star?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "You wanted to be a star?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "I think when I was younger, I wanted to be a star, until I became a star, and then it's a lot of work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I saw that parallel, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "How much do you think it scarred you or did it just drive you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I think it did scar me more than it drove me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Have you been able to find out a lot about him and his character and his life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What did that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "That he was telling me something.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "WP", ",", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "What was he telling you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "It was this message that, you know, no matter what, love is the answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Does the wider world know all of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "You didn't ask how long it lasted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "How long does it need to last to qualify for proper love, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Oh, maybe seven.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "But there is something that you recognize in someone's past, and it's -- it's a void, that you're recognizing, don't you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "I think -- and I think you'd become -- I'm sure you are the same, but you are parentally curious, because you never knew this person, who yet despite that, was such a pivotal part of your life, clearly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Or was there a sense always of jealousy that you were leading the kind of life, perhaps, she dreamt of herself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "She was a wonderful singer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Did you feel that you had reconciled things with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Basically, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Do you remember?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "It was something that she made a record of when she -- when I was 13 and she took me, but it was really because she made the record and then I was able to make the record when I was 13.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "''", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Do you think she was proud of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "You know what it was, I used to say, ma, how come you never told me, \"I love you\", you never said those words or really hugged me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "How are you with your son?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Oh, I just -- I think everything he does is great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Doesn't he have a gorgeous voice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "He does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Have you never seen it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Redford"]}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NNP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "-- Redford that when he came in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1968"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Democratic National Convention"], "LOCATION": ["Berkeley"]}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "What would have happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "It was just a very interesting story about through their daughter and her political activism at Berkeley in 1968 and the Democratic National Convention, which is very interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "I kept sending you articles, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "You did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Your man didn't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "No, no, no, I don't have a horse in the race.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "My argument with you was I wondered whether Mitt Romney could be better for the American economy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Oh, my God, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "No, you know why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "You were having none of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Supreme Court"]}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Why have you been so consistent in support of Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "I can't even imagine thinking about what would happen to the Supreme Court if a Republican were the president, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "What does that tell you about the American people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Because the people -- the people are getting smarter, they are going, I don't like this -- all this amount of money spent on this election.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Have you ever been in love with a Republican?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Could you ever be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Or I imagine one of them when he came out so vocally for gay rights, finally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "What else has he done, are you saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Yeah, that you are particularly proud of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "That's so scary, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I thought that pretty unsettling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Some men, mostly women, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "You feel that there is any form of real equality yet in America for women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Well, we are one of the last countries to ever think of having a woman be president, but I think that's possible now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Do you think Hillary is likely to run?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "I don't know, but I hope after a four-year rest that she would run.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "It is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "I want to know who you think the greatest movie star in the world is, ever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Yeah, when you look at yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "I'm so objective when I look at myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Do you see a beautiful woman there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Not particularly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Have you ever looked in the mirror and thought you look beautiful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "From certain angles.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Which is your best angle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Well, my left.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", ",", "PRP$", ":"], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Because my eyes don't look as cross-eyed sometimes or my nose is better, my--", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RBS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Have you resisted the sort of self-masticated plunge into plastic surgery that so many American female stars feel compelled to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "I don't trust most people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlon Brando"]}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Who do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Marlon Brando.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Oh, no question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Do you doubt that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "No, I don't, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBD", ",", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Marlon Brando would?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "He called me up once, and said, sing me a song.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlon Brando"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "And what did you have to sing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 484, "question": "What did you sing him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "I sang a song called \"Nobody's Heart Belongs to Me.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "What did he say at the end of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "I don't remember that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Where did you go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "He wanted to take me to the desert, to see the wild flowers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "You turned down Marlon Brando?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Yeah, I thought, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlon Brando"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "How did he take rejection?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "He was fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Yes, because it's just almost, I would say, musical perfection.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "What do you feel when you see it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I can't see what you see, I really can't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "And forgot the words to a few big songs, and it freaked you out so much, you did not perform again live for how long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "27 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Have you even been a terrible diva?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "What the hell is a diva, I don't even know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Have you ever been one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Have you ever screamed at people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Oh, yes, I screamed at people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Are you a perfectionist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "I am proud to say I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Are you a naturally person, or can you just completely relax if you want to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I think more so now, I can relax.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "You want to drive cross-country with me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "TREISAND: Don't you think I might get on your nerves a little bit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "No, it was just a thought, and if you don't want to do it, then fine, I don't want to push you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "Could you ever imagine doing a road trip with your son like that for a week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "Yeah, I could imagine going it with him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "Yeah, because we're just too similar.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "You know what that is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "How did they go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "It actually brings us closer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "Probably.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "Did you think that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "Well, it's not conscious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "Do you ever look at it and think, yes, I've not done badly for a young girl from Brooklyn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "Every once in a while.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Brooklyn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "Did you like making that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "It's not a challenge, put it that way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 812, "question": "47?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 813, "answer": "I'm 47.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP"], "qSentId": 816, "question": "When you were a baby, you wanted to do an interview with me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 817, "answer": "Yes!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]